Banks McLaurin, Jr. stereograph collection
DeGolyer Library
- Boxed Travel Sets, Series 16:
  - Boxed Sets (Box 18)
    - Niagara Falls, Vol. I. Stereoscopic Library. Underwood Underwood. Set of 18 in box with descriptive book and map, Niagara Through the Stereoscope. Some stereos have UU labels; some have UU patents and Keystone labels – 7 and 11 to be exact. Bought at Gainesville Antique Mall on 12/19/91.
      - K (1) 5395 General view of the Falls – Maid of Mist at landing
      - U (2) 5396 Tourists viewing the falls from Prospect Point
      - U (3) 5397 Looking down over the bluff at Prospect Point
      - K (4) 5398 American Falls from below
      - U (5) 5399 Maid of the Mist at Large
      - U (6) 5400 The falls from the Maid of the Mist, S-70
      - U (7) 5401 Niagara – S.W. from the tower
      - U (8) 5402 Rapids above Niagara Falls, S-74
      - K (9) 5403 American and Luna Falls
      - U (10) 5404 Looking into Cave of the Winds, S-73
      - K (11) 5405 American Falls and Rock of Ages
      - K (12) 5406 American Falls from Canadian side
      - K (13) 5407 Horseshoe Falls from above
      - K (14) 5408 Autumn on Niagara's banks – SW towards falls S-77
      - K (15) 5409 Dixon crossing on a rope below the falls
      - K (16) 5410 Looking at the waters below the falls
      - K (17) 5411 Whirlpool Rapids below the falls
      - K (18) 5412 Looking over the Whirlpool down river from falls
    - Real Children, Vol. I? Stereoscopic Library. Keystone View Co. The first 8 stereos were in box; added five more from what I had, which fit the name on the box. It appears that 5 more would fill the box as other groups on Grand Canyon, Yosemite and Niagara Falls hold.
      - R10 1028 Fun for the boys and girls on their playground, Copenhagen
      - R13 (9)1055 Monument of Catherine II Alexander Theater. St. Petersburg
      - R17 10850 Little folks studying in village school, Ramur, Palestine
      - R20 (24) 7663 school boys having their school outdoors, Burma
      - R30 (92) 9427 Primary School, Jalapa, Mexico
      - R31 8051 Beauford Road from Quebec to Montmorenei, Canada
      - R33 11405 Moki Indians in their strange home, Wolpi, AZ, USA
      - R35 6939 The snow fort and its gallant defenders
      - Added:
      - 21330 (1) Indians - Playing Indian
      - 33834 (2) Children – Philippine Negritos Fishing for Frogs
      - 14061 (5) Japanese children reading a newspaper
      - 17475 (11) American children at play (USA)
      - 24710 (19) Children - Czechoslovakian children
      - R1 8094 Peasant Children on the Steps of the Temple of Vesta, Rome, Italy
      - R4 11404 Little neighbors "building houses" near Cathedral, Burgos, Spain
      - R5 6 Praca (Square) and Column of Dom Pedro IV, Lisbon, Spain
      - R7(90)10012 The River Teme and charming green country around Ludlow, England
      - Other stereos on children
      - 613 Innocence abroad, ca. 1898
      - 26401 Farmer's wife churning butter
      - 11404 A June Carnival – Dancing Round the Daisy Pole, ca. 1900
      - W21327 P46 Winter – Boys playing fort in the snow
      - 17512 P14 Ready to go on picnic
      - R9(92)1236 Stored castle of the Brothers, and Moat, Bornhofen on the Rhine, S. from river-road, Germany
      - R11(53)653 Children at play in a farmer’s field before terraced Tvinde water fall, near Vossevangen, Norway
      - R12(59)865 An old well vine-shaped porch and little folds at home-Lerdal, beside Lake Siljam, Sweden
      - R14(50)1920 An Austrian hamlet, Val Ampezzo
      - R19(26)3589 Children are children the wide world round-playing Hop Scotch in Cashmere
      - R24(65)10293 Christmas holiday pleasures at the Fern Tree Bower, near Hobart, Tasmania
      - R29(90) Young Banana Plants-growing prospects of a Country Home near Mayaguez, Porto Tico
      - R32(43)4697 The worlds most unique inhabitants-Esquimaux with summer tents, Greenland
      - R3?(20)1524 Beside the Zider Zee-thrifty Dutch villagers on the fisherman’s wharf at Volendam, Holland
    - Russia. Underwood Underwood Publishers. Set of 100, most stereos ca. 1897, 1898, and 1899 with one dated 1904. 26 missing. Were in a library, call number 914.7. On back of stereos the number 52934 stamped. This set was purchased Oct. 8, 1992 for $85.80 at Past Time Antiques, 1059 Main Street, Cambria, CA 93428.
      - 1-9 Missing
      - 10 Allegorical Statue – Man conquering the Brute, Fontanka Bridge, St. Petersburg
      - 11 Boischaya Morskaya, the street leading to the Czar’s Winter Palace, St. Petersburg
      - 12 Monument to Alexander I, Arch of Triumph, and the Staab Building, St. Petersburg
      - 13 The Imperial Winter Palace from Nevsky Prospect, St. Petersburg
      - 14 The Peristyle of the Hermitage, St. Petersburg
      - 15 Gallery of Modern Sculpture, in the Hermitage, St. Petersburg
      - 16 The Imperial Summer Garden, St. Petersburg, 1062
      - 17 Equestrian Statue of Peter the Great, St. Petersburg
      - 18 St. Isaac’s Cathedral, St. Petersburg – the largest Church in Russia, 1064
      - 19 St. Petersburg, Russia, from the Dome of Isaac’s Cathedral
      - 20 The Admiralty Building, University and Vasilii Ostrof, St. Petersburg
      - 21 Riding School of the Life Guard, Senate, Academy and Vasilii Ostrof, St. Petersburg
      - 22 St. Catherine Church and Holy Water Procession, St. Petersburg – Aug. 1st, 1897
      - 23 Missing
      - 24 Palace Bridge, Admiralty and St. Isaac’s Church from the Exchange, St. Petersburg
      - 25 Missing
      - 26 Missing
      - 27 Burian Place of the Czars, in the Peter Paul Church of the Fortress, St. Petersburg
      - 28 Making Hay in Russia
      - 29 The Avenue of the Fountains, Imperial Palace, St. Petersburg
      - 30 Peterhof Palace, Russia, the Czar’s Home in the summer
      - 31 Equipages before Peterhof Palace, Russia, the Czar’s Home in the summer
      - 32 The Fountains from Peterhof Palace, summer residence of the Czar of Russia 1078
      - 33 Their Majesties, the Empresses of Russia and Germany, driving through Peterhof Park
      - 34 Narcissus Fountain on Empress Island, Colonists Park, Palace Grounds of Peterhof
      - 35 Missing
      - 36 Missing
      - 37 Founding of the Alexander Hospital, St. Petersburg, Russia by the Emperor and Empress of Germany, 1897
      - 38 The Czar of Russia and the French President laying the Corner Stone of the Troytzky Bridge, St. Petersburg
      - 39 Holy Trinity Church with the Monument built of Turkish Cannon, St. Petersburg
      - 40 Missing
      - 41 The Largest of the Imperial Palaces, Tsarskoe Selo
      - 42 The Lake and Island in the Imperial Grounds, Tsarskoe Selo
      - 43 The Imperial Majesties, the Czar and Czarina of Russia, Krasnoe Selo - Aug. 25th, 1897
      - 44 Review of the Russian Troops by the French President, Krasnoe Selo, Russia – Aug. 25th, 1897
      - 45 Foreign Representatives at the Military Review, Krasnow Selo – Aug. 25th, 1897
      - 46 Their Majesties the Czar and Czarina of Russia and the Pres. of France, Krasnoe Selo
      - 47 From Sparrow Hills, Napoleon’s first view of Moscow
      - 49 Temple of Our Savior, the Greatest Church in Moscow
      - 48 The Historical Novo Devitchi Convent, near Moscow
      - 50 Missing
      - 51 Missing
      - 52 Moscow, the Pride of the Czars, s.e. from the Temple of our Savior
      - 53 The Moskwa River and the shimmering spires of "Holy Moscow"
      - 54 Missing
      - 55 The Kremlin, Moscow
      - 56 The Kremlin Wall and Tower of the Sacred Gate, Moscow, 1102
      - 57 Spaski Vorota, Sacred Gate of the Kremlin, where all heads must be uncovered, Moscow
      - 58 Missing
      - 59 Tower of Ivan the Great and Cathedral of the Archangel Michael, Kremlin, Moscow, 1105
      - 60 The King of Bells (200 tons), Moscow
      - 61 Holy Moscow, from the Tower of Ivan the Great, Russia, 1107
      - 62 Cathedral of the Assumption where Emperors of Russia are Crowned, Moscow
      - 63 Cathedral of the Annunciation, where the Czars have been baptized and married, Moscow
      - 64 The Great Czar Cannon, Moscow
      - 65 The Great Bazaar in the Kitai Gorod, Moscow
      - 66 Central Entrance to the Great Bazaar, Kitai Gorod, Moscow
      - 67 Missing
      - 68 The Market in the Kitai Gorod, Moscow
      - 69 Romanoff House, Moscow, birthplace of Michael, first Tsar of the reigning dynasty
      - 70 The Rumiantsof Museum, Moscow
      - 71 Petrofski Imperial Palace, Moscow
      - 72 The Great Sunday Market of Moscow
      - 73 Church of the Nativity, one of the 800 Greek Churches in Old Moscow
      - 74 Nijni-Novgorod, Summer Market Place of all Nations
      - 75 Interior of the Church of the Nativity of the Holy Virgin Nijni-Novgorod
      - 76 The Floating Bridge over the Oka and the Fair of Nijni-Novgorod
      - 77 Missing
      - 78 Missing
      - 79 Missing
      - 80 Chinese Row in the Market of all Nations, Nijni Novgorod
      - 81 Siberian Hides and the village of the Tartars, Nijni Novgorod
      - 82 Missing
      - 83 Principal Street of ancient Kief, Little Russia
      - 84 Alexandrofski Slope and the winding Dnieper River, Kief
      - 85 The St. Vladimir Monument and the murmuring Dnieper, Kief
      - 86 The Podol portion of ancient Kief
      - 87 Missing
      - 88 The Fairy Land of Little Russia
      - 89 Interior of the Vladimir Cathedral, Kief, most beautifully decorated Church in Russia
      - 90 The Birth of Jesus, in Vladimir Cathedral, Kief
      - 91 The Resurrection in Vladimir Cathedral, Kief
      - 92 Missing
      - 93 The handsome Opera House of Odessa, Russia, one of the finest in Europe
      - 94 The Cathedral – Odessa, Russia
      - 95 Interior of the Cathedral – Odessa, Russia
      - 96 The Great Staircase, Odessa, Russia
      - 97 Wheat for export at South Russia’s great seaport, Odessa
      - 98 Overlooking the extensive salt fields (20,000 tons) of Solinen, Russia
      - 99 A reservoir at the Salt Fields, Solinen
      - 100 The Black Sea from the Russian Coast
        Note: this set was purchased 8 Oct. 1992 for $85.80 at Past Time Antiques – 1059 Main Street, Cambria, CA 93428.
  - Box Sets (Box 19)
    - Scenic America. Vol. III., Vol. IV. Stereographic Library. Keystone View Co. 35 of a set of 100. Set in box is numbered 3 to 50; box on outside says "101-200."
      - 3 W29573 Splendor of Entrance Hall, Congressional Library, Wash. D.C., ca. H.C.A. White
      - 6 V26112 Southwest to White House from State, War Navy Bldg., Wash., D.C., ca. UU
      - 2 26100 Washington from an airplane, Wash., D.C.
      - 8 H151 26334 The Lincoln Memorial, Wash., D.C.
      - 11 32566 Bancroft Hall, US Naval Academy, Annapolis, MD
      - 12 32833 Mt. Vernon Place, Baltimore, MD
      - 13 86 V23470 Deck of an Oyster Boat, Chesapeake Bay, MD
      - 14 32836 Rodney Square and DuPont Bldg., Wilmington, DE
      - 15 T28 32569 Looking north on Broad Street, Philadelphia, PA
      - 19 32831 Washington Memorial Chapel, Valley Forge, PA
      - 18 23145 Washington's Headquarters at Valley Forge, PA
      - 20 29576 America's Foremost Seaside Resort, Atlantic City, NJ
      - 21 32828 Old Nassau Hall, Princeton Univ., Princeton, NJ
      - 22 T32 32276 From Commerce Broad Sts., Newark, NJ
      - 23 16730 Palisade of the Hudson, NJ
      - 24 32775 George Washington Bridge, World's greatest, NY City
      - 25 32364 Hudson River Valley, Bear Mountain Bridge, NY
      - 26 32360 Cadets at West Point, NY
      - 27 32823 Manhattan from the air, NY City
      - 28 T38 23155 North on Broadway past Trinity Church, NY City
      - 30 32400 T The Great White Way, NY City
      - 34 T43 26494 Coney Island, NY's Island most popular beach resort, NYC
      - 32 32703 Manhattan's skyline from Brooklyn Bridge, NY City
      - 39 T76 32578 T Capital of the Old Dominion, Richmond, VA
      - 40 T78 32218 Home of Thomas Jefferson, Monticello, VA
      - 41 W29577 T Natural Bridge in VA
      - 42 32839 Asheville, NC Land of the Sky
      - 43 23482 Magnolia Gardens, near Charleston, SC
      - 44 32187 North on Peachtree St., Atlanta, GA
      - 45 107 13747 Chipping a turpentine tree, GA
      - 46 V23238 Coconut trees at Palm Beach, FL
      - 48 32313 Singing tower at Mountain Lake, FL
      - 47 26850 The Royal Poinciana, Palm Beach, FL
      - 49 26826 Miami's skyline from the harbor, FL
      - 50 26587 Franklin St., Tampa, FL
      - Delaware 5
      - Dist. of Columbia 4
      - Florida 5
      - Georgia 2
      - Maryland 3
      - New Jersey 4
      - New York 2
      - New York City 6
      - North Carolina 1
      - Pennsylvania 3
      - South Carolina 1
      - Virginia 3
    - Seventy-two Perfect Stereographs. H. C. White Co. Housed in black box.
    - Switzerland Underwood Underwood. Set of 100 in a Keystone box; most of the slides are U U labeled – the few that are not noted "key" in front of the numbers. All subjects in Switzerland. Bought at Gainesville antique mall on 12/19/91.
      - [1] 1736 [S697] Falls of the Rhine Laufen Castle
      - [2] 1737 St. Gall, historic and beautiful
      - [3] 1738 Interior of the Monastery Church, St. Gall
      - [4] 1739 Zurich, the metropolis of Switzerland
      - [5] 1740 The village favorite
      - Key [6] 1741 Lucerne and her beautiful lake
      - [7] 1742 Picturesque bridge, tower church, Lucerne
      - [8] 1743 The Lion of Lucerne
      - [9] 1744 [S698] Lucerne the lofty Pilatus
      - [10] 1745 [S699] Alpine elevator to the clouds, Mt. Pilatus
      - [11] 1746 The summit of historic Pilatus
      - [12] 1747 [S700] The backbone of Europe from the summit of Pilatus
      - Key [13] 1748 Lake of Lucerne from Axenstein
      - Key [14] 1749 Sisikon and the mighty Uri-Rothstock
      - Key [15] 1750 The bold Axenstrasse hewn from cliffs, Lake Lucerne
      - [16] 1751 [S702] Tunnels of the Axenstrasse, overhanging Lake Lucerne
      - Key [17] 1752 [S703] The river Aare at Berne
      - [18] 1753 Berne and her great mountain shain
      - [19] 1754 [S704] Principal street and the old clock, Berne
      - [20] 1755 At the village fountain
      - [21] 1756 A Swiss home and its home-maker
      - Key [22] 1757 Ancient Thun and its lake from the castle
      - [23] 1758 Interlaken and Jungfrau
      - [24] 1759 Grindlewald Valley, the Wetterhorn Schreckhorn
      - Key [25] 1760 Staubbach Falls, Lauterbrunnen Valley
      - [26] 1761 The Eiger and Lauterbrunnen Valley
      - [27] 1762 Murren, loftiest of Switzerland’s hamlets
      - [28] 1763 The Breithorn and Tschingelhorn, upper Lauterbrunnen
      - [29] 1764 [S705] Jungfrau from the summit of Scheidegg
      - [30] 1765 Grindlewald Valley and the Wetterhorn
      - [31] 1766 Glacier basin below the Fiescherhorn
      - [32] 1767 Ascent of Jungfrau – crossing the Glacier
      - [33] 1768 [S706] A country road
      - [34] 1769 Upper Grindlewald glacier
      - [35] 1770 [S707] Youthful years and maiden beauty
      - [36] 1771 [S708] The wonderful gorge of the river Aare
      - [37] 1772 Looking down the Rhine valley from Disentis
      - [38] 1773 Looking down the Via Mala toward Thusis Rhine Valley
      - [39] 1774 Piz Bernina Roseg, Engadine
      - [40] 1775 Bella Vista, Piz Bernina Morteratsch Glacier, Engadine
      - [41] 1776 Peaks of Palu, Engadine
      - [42] 1777 Upper Engadine
      - [43] 1778 The Engadine, looking S.W. from Hahnensee
      - [44] 1779 [S709] The descent to Italy from Maloja Pass, Engadine
      - [45] 1780 Engineering feats on St. Gothard RR, Italian side
      - [46] 1781 St.Gothard R.R. at Wassen
      - [47] 1782 Grimsel Pass Oberaarhorn Finsteraanhorn
      - [48] 1783 View of Rhone Valley from Furka Pass
      - [49] 1784 Looking south from Eggishorn over Rhone Valley
      - [50] 1785 [S710] Fischer Glacier Oberaaehorn NE from Eggishorn
      - [51] 1786 [S711] The great Aletsch Glacier Marjelen Lake
      - [52] 1787 [S712] Edge of Aletsch Glacier Marjelen Lake
      - [53] 1788 An ocean of Ice, great Aletsch Glacier
      - [54] 1789 Looking N. down the Visp valley from near Stalden
      - [55] 1790 [S713] The Alpine Spirit’s sanctuary – Zermatt
      - [56] 1791 Matterhorn from pathway above Zermatt
      - [57] 1792 Matterhorn, seen from the Schwarzsee
      - [58] 1793 Gorner Glacier, Monte Rosa
      - [59] 1794 Zermatt from the Schwarzsee
      - [60] 1795 "Lion of the Alps," the Matterhorn
      - [61] 1796 [S714] Breithorn, Monte Rosa group from the Gornergott
      - [62] 1797 Lyskamm, Monte Rosa group from Gornergrat
      - [63] 1798 Summit of Mt. Rosa from Gornergrat
      - [64] 1799 Zermatt from the Schwarzsee
      - [65] 1800 [R2] Swiss hamlet near eternal snow – Saas-fee
      - [66] 1801 A typical alpine home – Saas-fee
      - [67] 1802 Industry and simplicity – Saas-fee
      - [68] 1803 Sion, with its medieval homes and castles
      - [69] 1804 Inn where Napoleon stopped, Bourg St. Pierre
      - [70] 1805 [S715] Monastery and dogs, Great St. Bernard Pass
      - [71] 1806 Great St. Bernard Pass, Lake Monastery
      - [72] 1807 Eastern Side Mt. Blanc range
      - [73] 1808 Ancient castle of Chillon, Lake Geneva
      - [74] 1809 [S716] Lake Geneva and the Dent du Midi
      - [75] 1810 Village of Montreus on Lake Geneva
      - [76] 1811 Sunset, Lake Geneva
      - [77] 1812 Lake Geneva – bridges across the Rhone
      - [78] 1813 Balmat, first to ascend Mt. Blanc, Chamonix
      - [79] 1814 [S717] Frightful Alpine precipices toward Mt. Blanc
      - [80] 1815 [S718] Mount Blanc, from the Brivent
      - [81] 1816 Climbing heights above Valley of Chamonix
      - [82] 1817 Ascent of Mont Blanc, Bossons Glacier
      - [83] 1818 Tunnel in Bossons Glacier
      - [84] 1819 Ascent of Mt. Blanc, at Pierre Pointue
      - [85] 1820 Ascent of Mt. Blanc, crossing Bossons Glacier
      - [86] 1821 Ascent of Mt. Blanc, ice cliffs on Bossons Glacier
      - [87] 1822 Ascent of Mt. Blanc, from Grands Mulets hut
      - [88] 1823 Ascent of Mt. Blanc, looking back to Grands Mulets
      - [89] 1824 Ascent of Mt. Blanc, Dome du Gouter
      - [90] 1825 Ascent of Mt. Blanc, resting at Grand Plateau
      - [91] 1826 Ascent of Mt. Blanc, Valley refuge hut
      - [92] 1827 Summit of Mt. Blanc, highest point in Europe
      - [93] 1828 [S719] Descent of Mt. Blanc, crevasse near summit
      - [94] 1829 Mer de Glace and Grandes Jorasses
      - [95] 1830 Ascent of Aig. du Tacul
      - [96] 1831 [S720] Ascent of Aig. du Tacul, s.w. to Aig du Geant
      - [97] 1832 Ascent of Aig. du Tacul
      - [98] 1833 The Mauvais Pas Mer de Glace
      - [99] 1834 [S721] Mer de Glace with mountains in background
      - [100] 1835 [S722] Great Ice Fall at end of Mer de Glace
    - Tour of the World, Vol. I. Stereographic Library. Keystone View Co. Date of issue: ca. 1932. Set of 50. Bought 11/19/91 at East Fork Mall, Sunnyvale, TX for $60 + tax.
      - Front # (back #) Top # left front
      - 1089 (355-3012) 205 Anne Hathaway's Cottage Shottery, England
      - 8639 (9781) 779 The Ancient Sphinx of Giza, Egypt
      - W8801 (W8801) 654 The Paderewski Villa, Warsaw, Poland (ca. H.C. White)
      - 9869 (9869) 774 Looking up the Great Pyramid, Egypt
      - 12568 (12568) 881 The Taj Mahal, Agra, India
      - 12700 (12700) 190 Burn's Cottage, Ayr, Scotland
      - 12804 (128040 107 Harvesting bananas, Costa Rica
      - 13577 (38178) 1111 Grand Canyon of the Yellowstone, WY
      - 14455 ( ) 157 Eccentric growth of Cocoa Pods, Dominica, BWI
      - V14498 (V14498) 167 Cutting Tobacco near Habana, Cuba
      - V14730 (V14730) 946 Rice Planters at work, Japan
      - 14739 (14739) 928 A country girl among the Tea Fields, Schizuoka, Japan
      - 16648 (16648) 1200 Full moon, Yerkes Observatory
      - 19671 (19671) 705 Garden of Gethsemane and Mt. Of Olives, Jerusalem
      - 20742 (20742) 825 Victoria Falls, Rhodesia, South Africa
      - 20757 (20757) 831 Mammough Pits of South Africa's Greatest Diamond Mine
      - 21038 (21308) 1081 The Indian Village of Kasaan, Alaska
      - V21911 (V21911) 124 Llamas, Cerro de Pasco, Peru
      - 21941 (21941) 119 Panama Hats being woven, Tabacunda, Ecuador
      - 23796 (23796) 80 Carved Altar of Guadalupe, Tepozotland, Mexico
      - 23842 (238420 963 The Great Wall of China n. Nankow Pass, China
      - 23870 (23870) 995 Canal between Canton and the Is. of Shameen, China
      - V24056 (11064) 1009 Filipino farmer with water buffalo, Luzcon, P. Is.
      - V24316(C962-V24316) 1031 Kangaroo, Melbourne, Victoria, Australia
      - 25249 (25216) 356 Washday in Volendam, Holland
      - V25486 (V25486) 231 Westminster Abbey, London, England
      - (26557) 5006 1066 Wanona Tunnel Tree, Mariposa Grove Yosemite, CA
      - V27402 (V27402) 898 Elephants Piling Teak Logs, Rangoon, Burma
      - V27427 (V27427) 867 Carved Temple of Vimala Sah., Mt. Abu, India
      - V27701 (V27701) 744 Palace of Nebuchadnezzar, Iraq
      - 29609 (290609) 1126 Grand Canyon from El Tovar on South Rim, AZ
      - 29575 (29575) 16 Independence Hall, Philadelphia, PA
      - 29609 (29600) 412 Eiffel Tower and Champs de Mars from Trocadero, Paris
      - 29639 (3178) 405 Restored Cathedral of Reims, France
      - 27828 (27828) 306 Grundivigs Church, Kobenhavn, Denmark
      - 30063 (30063) 313 Potsdammer Platz at night, Berlin, Germany
      - 32229 (32229) 4 The Dazzling Dome of the Capital at night, Washington, D.C.
      - 32741 (32721) 1072 Mt. Hood, or from an airplane
      - 32792 (32792) 1137 The Worlds Highest Bridge, Royal Gorge, CO
      - 33280 (33280) 717 Church of the Nativity, Bethlehem, Palestine
      - 33329 (28757) 457 The Ramblas and its Flower Market, Barcelona, Spain
      - V33422 (V33422) 579 Cathedral of Milan, Italy
      - 33516 (33516) 1132 Crystal Springs Dome, Carlsbad Caverns, NM
      - 34080 (34080) 1 Washington, DC from an airplane
      - 34094 (34094) 668 Pushkin Monument, Moscow, USSR
      - 34120 (34120) 1196 Airplane view of Niagara Falls, NY
      - 34174 (34174) 29 Empire State Bldg., NY City from the air
      - 34885 (32822) 64 The Alamo, San Antonio, TX
      - 37171 (37171) 1046 Hawaiian Pineapple Ready for the Cannery
      - 38221 (38232) 110 Ships Passing through the Panama Canal, Panama
    - Tour of the World, Vol. I, Vol. II, Stereographic Library. Boxed set of 102.
      - Belgium
      - 396 25586 River Meuse and Parc de la Citadel, Namur
      - 390 25593 Royal Palace, Brussels
      - 399 33273 The Fortress and City as Restored since the War, Dinant
      - 383 25590 Menin Gate, Ypres
      - 369 25585 Notre Dame Cathedral Harbor, Antwerp
      - 373 25592 Guild Houses on The Grande Place, Antwerp
      - Bermuda
      - 166 20591 Where It Is Always Summer - The Green Isles of Bermuda...
      - Brazil
      - 144 V21901T Rio de Janeiro
      - 143 21831 Avendia Biera Mar, Rio de Janeiro
      - T57 21859 Rua Visconte, Rio de Janeiro
      - Canada
      - H48 W27120 Chateau Frontenac, Quebec
      - Chile
      - 134 21861 Inca Lake
      - T264 21865 Bay City of Valparaiso
      - Denmark
      - 301 27843 Kronbork Castle and Harbor, Helsinger
      - 308 27831 A drizzly day in Jutland near Kolding
      - Ecuador
      - 115 21938 Waterfront at Guayaquil
      - France
      - 411 24991 Arch of Triumph, Paris
      - 421 18777 Palace of Versailles
      - 441 32734 T Among the gardens of Mentone
      - 415 V24810 Old City Island and Seine, Paris
      - 434 3189 Monument to American soldiers, St. Nazaire
      - 429 29641 The Pledge at Deauville
      - 416 24818 Notre Dame Cathedral, Paris
      - 412 29609 T (29600) Eiffel Tower, Paris
      - 422 18781 Clemenceau, Wilson Lloyd George leaving Versailles
      - French West Indies
      - 156 14439 T Coffee pickers, Guadalupe
      - Germany
      - 329 30047 Oberammergau
      - 348 30065 Cathedral of Cologne
      - 345 33243 Where the Moselle enters the Rhine, Coblenz